paddocktalk.com 2014-11-22

# PaddockTalk :: F1, Formula 1, NASCAR, IndyCar, MotoGP, Le Mans, And More!

What is a Privacy Policy? 

PaddockTalk LLC created a privacy policy to show our dedication and commitment to the privacy of the users of our website. Please read the following to gain an understanding of our privacy policy. If you have any questions whatsoever regarding this policy, please send us an email inquiry at admin@paddocktalk.com. A PaddockTalk LLC representative will respond to your query as soon as possible. 

What information do we collect from users and how is it used? 

At PaddockTalk.com we do not collect any personal information whatsoever, unless you choose to share such information. Examples of such information that you might provide us are your name and email address for purposes of our TalkBack(Send & Ask Qs), (ie. Letters to the Editor) 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Submitting Materials for Publication to PaddockTalk LLC 

All letters, articles, photos, or other materials sent to PaddockTalk LLC will be treated as unconditionally assigned for publication and copyright purposes and subject to PaddockTalk's right to edit and comment editorially. By sending such information you agree to these terms. Sensitive information such as email address, phone number and address will be edited if we choose to publish a letter to protect the privacy of the user. If you do choose to share personal information via some form of correspondence, such information will not be sold or rented to others whatsoever. 

Ptalkforum.com & PaddockTalk.com Forums 

This site makes forums and message boards available to its users. You are not required to provide any personal information in order to use these areas but you may choose to do so. Please remember that any information that you choose to disclose in these areas will be publicly available; thus, you should exercise caution when deciding whether to disclose personal information. PaddockTalk LLC cannot accept any responsibility for ensuring the privacy of information that you choose to disclose in these areas. 

Correspondence 

If you correspond with us via E-mail, we may gather the information in a file specific to you. We only collect the information that you provide to us. We will not sell or rent the information that you share with us to others. Like many other websites, PaddockTalk LLC collects information about users' utilization and navigation of our site. This information helps us to design our site to better suit our users' needs. 

Does the PaddockTalk LLC website use cookies? If so, how are cookies used on the website? 

Cookies are small files placed on your computer that contain only a unique number. We use this number to recognize your computer when a user of your computer returns. Like most major websites, PaddockTalk.com uses cookies on certain pages of our site. These cookies strictly identify your computer and our cookies do not contain any personal information about you. 

What are the policies of linked sites and other third parties? 

This privacy policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Although you may link to other sites or third parties via our website, PaddockTalk LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties or the content of linked sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy policy whenever interacting with any website. 

How will I know about changes in the Privacy Policy? 

PaddockTalk LLC reserves the right to update this privacy policy from time to time. Please visit this page periodically so that you will be apprised of any changes. However, we will only use Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with the Privacy Policy that was in effect at the time the information was collected. If at any point we should decide to use that information differently, we will notify users by way of E-mail so that users can approve or disapprove of such use.
